（夢子(ゆめこ)）もちろん
- Naturally...
- To risk everything...
（綺羅莉(きらり)）全てを賭けた
（２人）ギャンブルを
...on a gamble.
（鈴井(すずい)）夢子
（夢子）あっ
Yumeko?
What you said yesterday...
are you serious?
（鈴井）昨日のあれ 本気なの？
You're up against
the student council president.
相手は あの生徒会長だよ
There's no telling
what she might make you do.
一体 何をやらされるか
分かったもんじゃない
（夢子）鈴井さん
（鈴井）あっ
Suzui?
心配してくださっているんですね
I see that you're concerned about me.
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
でもね
But you see,
I'm very sorry, but it's no good.
申し訳ありませんが ダメですよ
あんなごちそうを
目の前にぶら下げられては
Such a wondrous feast
dangling before me...
我慢できませんもの
I can't rein myself in.
I don't want to stop you. I'll watch you
gamble from the best seat in the house.
止めたいわけじゃないよ
いちばん近くで見たいんだ
夢子のギャンブルを
あっ
（鈴井）
僕は夢子に魅せられている
Yumeko's bewitched me.
（芽亜里(めあり)）あんたたち
Hey, you two.
How can you be so nonchalant?
（芽亜里）何 のんきにしてんのよ
（鈴井）うわ！
（芽亜里）
おしゃべりしてる暇があるわけ？
You think you have time to chat?
What's your game plan?
対策は？
What? My game plan?
（夢子）はあ 対策ですか？
（鈴井）う…
I mean your gamble with the president.
生徒会長とのギャンブルに
決まってんでしょ！
（伊月(いつき)）
まずは 特定の目しか出ないダイス
First, dice that only lands
on the number you want.
There's six to a set.
They have various applications.
６個セットで
いろんな種類に対応してます
お次は赤外線塗料付きのトランプ
Next up, playing cards
featuring infrared paint.
赤外線カメラを通して見れば
どのカードか一目瞭然！
With this infrared camera,
you can see which card is which.
そして これが私のお気に入り
Finally, this happens to be my favorite.
単純な仕組みで効果は絶大！
So simple-looking,
but mind-blowingly effective.
その名も南京虫(なんきんむし)
- It's called the Padlock Beetle--
- Wait.
（鈴井）ちょっと！
それって もしかして
イカサマするつもりなの？
Don't tell me you're planning
to cheat with those things.
はあ？
何 分かりきったこと聞いてんの
あんた
Why are you asking
such an obvious question?
あの生徒会長が相手なんだから
Her opponent's the president, after all.
このくらいやらなきゃ
いけませんよ〜
If we don't at least do this much,
it's over.
うっ
（夢子）
ご厚意はありがたいのですが
While I do appreciate your kindness...
イカサマをするつもりは
毛頭ありません
I have absolutely
no intention of cheating.
（伊月）え〜 なんでですか!?
Why not?
Because for my long-awaited gamble
with the president...
だって
念願の生徒会長とのギャンブルに
不純物は必要ありませんもの
I have no need for impurities.
（伊月）でっ
（芽亜里）ハア
まあ
そう言うと思ってたわ
I had a feeling you'd say that.
それならそれで
If that's how it's gonna be,
let's be sure we're ready.
覚悟を決めて
いきましょう
ハア そうですね
I guess you're right.
What? You're both coming with me, then?
え？
お２人共
一緒に来てくださるんですか？
あいつ 私にナメたこと
言ってくれたからね
She really talked down to me. I want
to see her go down in humiliating defeat.
ぶさまに負けるとこ
この目で見てやるわ
夢子先輩に賭けてますから！
Our money's on you, Yumeko-senpai.
はっ
（夢子）フッ 鈴井さん
（鈴井）あっ
Suzui?
（夢子）芽亜里さん 伊月さん
Mary? Itsuki?
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
〜
Welcome, everyone.
（清華(さやか)）
皆様 ようこそいらっしゃいました
会長がお待ちです
The president is waiting.
（ドアが開く音）
（清華）どうぞ
If you please.
Thank you for coming.
よく来てくれたわね
（夢子）お邪魔します 綺羅莉さん
Thank you for having us, Kirari.
余計な前置きはいらない
Let's dispense with the formalities.
Let's get this show on the road, shall we?
早いところ始めてしまいましょう
だって我慢できそうにない
Because there's no way
I can rein myself in.
こんなごちそうを
目の前にぶら下げられてはね
Not with such a wondrous feast
dangling before me.
（夢子）ウフッ
Ever since I first met you
at this academy...
あなたと初めて
この学園で出会ってから
ひょっとすると
もっとずっと前から
or maybe even long before that...
この日をどれだけ夢見たことか
You don't know how long
I've waited for this day.
（清華）
蛇喰(じゃばみ)夢子！
Yumeko Jabami.
（るな）
はい はい はい
はい はい
Right! All eyes on me!
ご注目！
ぱあ！
今日は わたくし 黄泉月(よもつき)るなが
I, Runa Yomozuki, am here
to serve as your referee today.
見届け人を
務めさせていただきま〜す
ニャハ ２人共
やる気満々で大変よろしい
You both look gung-ho.
That's what I like to see.
じゃ 手続き的なことは
ぱぱっと済ませていこっか
Let me give you a quick rundown
of the rules and let's go.
まず賭け金なんだけど
First, the stakes.
“全てを賭ける”って
具体的には何を賭けるのかな？
Putting everything on the line means
you'll be betting what, specifically?
夢子 ここでの生活は楽しい？
Yumeko, are you enjoying life here?
Yes, very much. An academy where
everything is determined by gambling.
ええ とっても
ギャンブルにより
全てが決まる学園
Heaven if you win, hell if you lose.
勝てば天国 負ければ地獄
誰もが
地を這(は)うリスクを抱えて生きている
Everyone living with the risk
of being reduced to groveling...
そんな場所
ほかのどこを探してもありません
You could never find a place
like this anywhere else.
百花王(ひゃっかおう)学園は
いわば私の理想郷です！
Hyakkao Academy is,
so to speak, my utopia.
気に入ってもらえてよかったわ
I'm so glad you like it.
外の世界のルールとは
隔絶された花園
A flower garden isolated
from the rules of the outside world.
唯一絶対の理(ことわり)は
ギャンブルによる弱肉強食
The one absolute law is survival
of the fittest through gambling.
誰もが必死に生きざるをえない
この学園を
Everyone is forced to live in desperation
at this academy, and I love it.
私は愛している
百花王学園は
私の作ったアクアリウム
Hyakkao Academy is an aquarium
of my own creation.
ウフフ すてきです
That's lovely.
学園には そのような思いが
込められていたのですね
I see that you've lavished much love
on this academy.
では
So...
（綺羅莉）それを
Let's bet that.
ニャハ
The one who loses this gamble
will never set foot in this school again.
このギャンブルで負けた者は
二度とこの学園の土を踏まない
（るな）そいつで合意？
（綺羅莉）ええ
- Are you down with that?
- Yes.
（るな）うん？
（夢子）はい
Yes.
No way.
そ… そんな！
（鈴井）ゆめ… うっ
（清華）会長！
- Yume--
- President!
Hold on a second. Isn't that too...?
お待ちください！
そのような… あっ
Hold up.
（芽亜里）
待って！ おかしいじゃない
That doesn't make sense.
勝っても得るものがないなんて
The winner won't gain anything.
それじゃ やる意味がない！
So, what's the point in playing?
そうかしら
Do you really think so?
ギャンブルとは
勝って得するためにやるものなの？
Do we gamble to win
in order to gain some advantage?
（芽亜里）あっ
（綺羅莉）
優秀なあなたは
そうなのかもしれない
That might be true
for someone competent like you.
But for most people,
it's a different story.
でも 多くの者にとっては違う
彼らは不利なギャンブルに
喜々として挑むの
They gladly take their chances
when the odds are against them.
人間とは不合理な
生き物であるというけれど
They say that humans
are irrational beings,
ここまで理(り)のない
行為も珍しい
but you rarely see
this level of illogical behavior.
Gambling produces nothing.
ギャンブルとは 何も生み出さない
By doing it, you only lose.
ただ失うだけの行為である
というのに
（２人）あっ
それでも私たちが
ギャンブルするのは
And yet, we still gamble...
because taking risks is so enjoyable.
リスクを負うのが
楽しいから
あっ！
Runa, kindly proceed, will you?
（綺羅莉）
るな 話を進めてちょうだい
（るな）アイアイ！
- Okey-doke. Itsuki, got any tarot cards?
- Why do you ask?
伊月ちゃん
タロットカード持ってない？
えっ なんでですか？
（るな）ギャンブルで使うから
We're using them for this gamble.
It's not like we don't have any here.
ここにも あるにはあるけど
自分たちが用意した物のほうが
安心でしょ？
But you'd feel more comfortable
with your own deck, right?
はっ あ… ありますけど
Sure, I do have a deck.
But because of what Yumeko said,
I left my trick tarot cards at home.
（伊月）
夢子に言われたから
細工したタロットは
置いてきちまったよ
もったいねえ〜
What a frickin' waste!
Thank you.
（るな）センキュ〜
さて 説明を始めさせてもらうわ
Now, then, let me explain
the rules to you.
For better or for worse, today's gamble...
よきにつけ あしきにつけ
今回のギャンブルは
私たちの運命を大きく変える
is sure to change our fate drastically.
だから占ってみましょう
- Let's divine the future.
- Here.
（るな）ほい
（綺羅莉）ギャンブルの名は
The name of this gamble is...
the Tarot Cards of Fate.
運命のタロットカード
さまざまな意味を持つ
22枚の大(だい)アルカナ
The 22 cards of the Major Arcana,
each with different meanings.
Three of us will each select one card.
この中から３人が
１枚ずつカードを選ぶ
大アルカナには それぞれ
０から21の数字が書いてあって
The cards of the Major Arcana
each bear a number from zero to 21.
これが得点になる
This will serve as the score.
ただし 引いた人間から見て
正位置ならプラス
If it's upright from the perspective
of the one who drew it, it'll be positive.
逆位置ならマイナスになるわ
And negative if it's reversed.
最終的に３枚の合計がプラスなら
夢子の勝利
If the total of the three cards
ends up positive, Yumeko wins.
If negative, I win.
マイナスなら私の勝利
ただし
However... there's just
one special card here, the Fool.
１枚だけ特別なカードがある
愚者
Since this card has no value,
it'll be the Joker.
ゼロであるこのカードは
ジョーカーとするわ
ほかのカードと関係なく
Regardless of the other cards,
if the Fool is upright, Yumeko wins.
愚者が正位置で出たら夢子
逆位置なら私の勝利
If it's reversed, I win.
This one card will sway the outcome
of this gamble.
これ１枚で勝敗が決する
運命のカード
There's always the chance
to pull off an upset.
常に逆転の可能性がある
ということね
タロットカードは
時の流れを占うことができる
Tarot cards can divine the flow of time.
私たちが手にする３枚のカードは
さしずめ 過去 現在 そして未来
The three cards
that we'll be drawing will be...
the Past, the Present...
and the Future.
占いましょう
Let's divine it...
what it is we truly think.
私たちが 真実 何を思うか
なしたことに意味はあったのか
What was the purpose
of everything we've done?
What kind of end will we be meeting?
どんな結末を迎えるのか
運命のカードに委ねましょう
Let's entrust it all
to these cards of fate.
Okay.
オッケ〜
じゃあ最後に その運命の３枚を
誰が引くのかだけど…
Lastly, who's gonna be drawing
those three cards of fate?
そうね
Let's see. Yumeko will draw the Present,
and I shall draw the Past.
現在は夢子
過去は私としましょうか？
そんな！ 会長が過去だ…
No way. You, draw the Past?
なんて…
I mean...
（綺羅莉）あと１枚 未来は…
And the last card, the Future...
（２人）うっ
あなた 名前は？
- You over there, what's your name?
- You mean me?
えっ ぼ… 僕ですか!?
鈴井涼太(りょうた)です
I'm Ryota Suzui.
All right, Ryota.
I want you to draw the Future.
いいわ 涼太
未来は あなたが引いて
はあ？ な… なんで僕が!?
- Why do you want me to?
- I like that idea.
（夢子）まあ それはいいですね！
- Suzui, I ask you to comply, as well.
- Yumeko.
鈴井さん 私からもお願いします！
（鈴井）夢子！
これは 私にとって
This might very well be the last gamble
I ever take part in at Hyakkao Academy.
百花王学園で最後になる
かもしれないギャンブルです
あっ
（鈴井）
夢子が 学園を去る
Yumeko... leave the academy?
この学園を去ることになる
かもしれないギャンブル
As a result of this gamble,
I may have to leave.
鈴井さんに
協力していただきたいんです
I'd like your cooperation as well, Suzui.
（鈴井）
そんな大役 僕には…
That big a role? I can't possibly...
そうだ！ あのときだって…
Wait. Just like that day...
（鈴井）分かったよ
All right.
I'll be the one to draw the Future.
僕が未来を引きます
決まりね
It's settled, then.
All right, why don't we get started?
それでは始めましょうか？
私たちの行く末を決する—
With the gamble
that will decide our destiny...
the Tarot Cards of Fate.
運命のタロット占いを
（２人）う…
（るな）準備 オッケ〜！
All systems go.
それじゃ 夢子ちゃんから！
Okay, you go first, Yumeko.
（るな）まずは 現在！
（夢子）はい
- Let's start with the Present.
- All right.
（夢子）う〜ん
（夢子）これにしましょう
（鈴井）あっ
I choose this one.
- You okay with its position, too?
- Yes.
（るな）
向きも それでいいのかな？
（夢子）はい
All right. Card... open!
じゃ カード オープン！
（芽亜里）
引くチャンスは たった３回
Only three chances to draw.
初回から
高いマイナス点なんて出したら
If she starts out with a huge negative,
it's gonna be hopeless.
目も当てられないが…
The Magician in the upright position.
正位置の魔術師！
得点は
And your score is... plus one point.
プラス１点！
い… １点
One point?
か〜
（るな）ニャハ
For a game you're risking everything on,
that's a pretty lame start, huh?
全てを賭けたギャンブルにしては
ショボい滑り出しかな〜
No, this is fine. Since all the cards
can be upright or reversed,
（芽亜里）
いや これでいい
全てのカードは 正と逆があるから
期待値としては常に０点
the expectation value is always zero.
As long as it's positive, she has an edge.
プラスであるだけで有利だ
All righty, let's keep moving.
（るな）
さあ どんどんいっちゃおう
お次は会長！
Next up, President.
And you'll be choosing the Past.
選ぶのは 過去！
（清華）う…
Yumeko, do you believe in fatalism?
（綺羅莉）
夢子 あなた 運命論は信じる？
（夢子）運命… ですか？
Do you mean fate?
I'm talking about the belief
that all events are predetermined.
あらかじめ 全ての物事は
そうなると決まっている
という話
う〜ん
そういうものがあれば
とってもロマンチックですね
If there were such a thing,
it would be romantic, wouldn't it?
私も同じ
I feel the same way.
Irreproducible and unscientific.
再現性がなく非科学的
でも運命は存在しないと断ずるのも
また非科学的
But it's also unscientific
to conclude that fate doesn't exist.
Do you know the record for the number
of consecutive blacks in roulette?
ルーレットで黒が連続で出た
回数の記録を知っていて？
（夢子）いいえ
（２人）ん…
No.
（綺羅莉）27回よ
Twenty-seven times.
確率にして およそ70億分の１
Odds of approximately
seven billion to one.
きっとそのルーレットを
担当していたディーラーは
I'm sure that roulette dealer
must've thought...
思ったでしょうね
"Oh, this machine must be broken."
“ああ この台は壊れているんだ”
だって そうでなければ
Otherwise,
you'd have to think that something
was making the balls land on black.
何かがボールを黒に入れている
としか思えない
フフッ
Unless it's something that can't
possibly happen, it can happen.
どんな事象も起こりえないこと
でないかぎりは起こりうる
たまたま
ごく薄い確率を引いたとき
When they beat the odds by the thinnest
of margins, people see it as fate.
人はそこに運命を見いだす
結局のところ 運命とは
At the end of the day, fate is merely what
comes up when something has happened,
起きてしまったことをどう呼ぶか
という話にすぎない
and you don't know what to call it.
Yumeko, I wonder what you would call this?
夢子
あなたはこれを
どう呼ぶのかしら？
逆位置の… 世界!?
It's a reversed... World?
The score is...
得点は？
Minus 21 points!
（るな）マイナス 21点！
あっ
（るな）さすが会長！
That's our president.
Who knew you'd draw that one?
ここでそれ引くかね
どんだけ持ってんのさ〜
Just how lucky are you, anyway?
ニャハハハハ！
そ… そんな！
No way! Minus 21 points at this stage?
You've got to be cheat--
ここでマイナス21点なんて
イカサマじゃ…
あ〜ん？ 伊月ちゃん
Itsuki, did you even hear
what the president was saying just now?
つか
さっきの会長の話 聞いてた？
ちょっと
不利な展開になったからって
Just because you're in the hole,
you're gonna call her a cheater?
イカサマ扱いかよ〜
（伊月）きっ
Hey, no worries, okay?
（るな）ニャハ 大丈夫だって
I'm totally neutral.
私は絶対中立！
今の会長の選択に
イカサマがなかったことは
I guarantee that there was no cheating
involved in the president's selection.
私が保証するよん！
そんなことより
現在の点数はマイナス20点
More importantly,
the score at this time is minus 20 points.
準備はいい？ 鈴井涼太君！
Are you ready, Ryota Suzui?
At this point, the only way for Yumeko
to win is for you to draw the Fool.
もはや夢子ちゃんが勝つには
君が愚者を正位置で引くしかない！
But you already know that, right?
そんなことは 分かってるよね〜
ニャハハハハ…
（芽亜里）
鈴井
Suzui... the only way to win
is to draw the Fool...
勝つには愚者を引くしか…
何か手がかりはないのか？
Isn't there any kind of clue?
（芽亜里）あっ
（伊月）これって！
Hey. That's...
（芽亜里）はっ
（伊月）あっ
Whoops. No good.
（るな）おっと！ ダメ ダメ〜
あくまで引くのは
鈴井君なんだからさ！
It's Suzui who's gonna draw
the card, remember?
しゃべんなとは言わないけど
I won't say anything, but if it looks like
you're coaching him, he's disqualified.
助言と判断したら
反則負けにすっからね！
さあ 鈴井君
未来を引いてちょうだい！
All right, Suzui. Please draw the Future.
（鈴井）
残りカードは20枚
There are twenty cards left.
Out of those twenty,
そのうち たった１枚である愚者を
I've got to draw the one and only Fool,
upright, no less.
しかも正位置で
引かなくちゃいけないんだから
The odds are 40 to one.
確率は 40分の１
そんなもの 僕に引けるとは…
I just can't believe I can do it.
（夢子）鈴井さん
（鈴井）あっ
Suzui? Please don't worry
about me and just draw.
どうぞ お気軽に引いてください
たとえ負けても
学園を去るのは私です
Even if we lose, I'm the one who'll
be leaving. This risk is mine alone.
そう これは私だけのリスク
私だけの痛みなのですから
This pain is mine alone.
あっ！
私は ただ粛々と
結果を受け入れるのみ
All I can do is accept the results calmly.
ウフフフ
夢子…
Yumeko...
それは違うよ
You're wrong. I told you, I'll be watching
from the best seat in the house.
（夢子）え？
（鈴井）言っただろ？
僕は いちばん近くで
夢子を見ていたい
夢子ともっと一緒にいたい
I want to spend more time with you.
This risk is just as much mine.
これは
僕のリスクでもあるんだ
（夢子）はっ！
（芽亜里）え！
（伊月）はあ！
（鈴井）
問題は
どのカードを引くかってことだけど
The question is which card I'm gonna draw.
It looks like those two noticed something.
２人は
さっき気付いたみたいだった
（伊月）今の聞きました!?
（芽亜里）うん…
- Did you hear what he just said?
- There's something I'm missing.
（鈴井）
つまり僕が見落としてる
何かがあるんだ
何か ヒントになるような…
Something. That might be a hint.
あっ
（伊月）
あっ 気付いたか？
Do you see it now? The remaining 20 cards
may look like there are no clues at all...
残る20枚のカード
手がかりが全くないように見えて…
but, actually, there's something sticking
to one of them.
（芽亜里）
実は１枚 光るものが付着している
あれは恐らくグロスか
それに類するものの跡
Most likely, it's gloss
or something similar.
故意でなければ
まず付かないだろう
It wouldn't be there
unless it was intentional.
（伊月）
ガン付け
A marked card. The kind of cheat where
you mark a card to draw one in your favor?
印を付けて
自分に有利なカードを引く
イカサマか？
No... and why not?
違う
なぜなら見届け人である黄泉月以外
誰もカードに触っていないから
Because no one but the referee,
Yomozuki, ever touched those cards.
あの瞬間を除いて！
Except for that one instant...
（芽亜里）
つまり あのカードは…
In other words, that card...
（伊月）
愚者！
The Fool.
黄泉月は 確かに真実を言っていた
Not that Yomozuki
wasn't telling the truth.
会長の選択に イカサマはない
The president wasn't cheating
when she drew that card.
会長はガン付けをしておきながら
そのカードを引かなかったんだ！
The president marked that card,
but she didn't draw it.
なぜ会長が
そんなことをしたのか分からないが
I have no idea why the president
would do such a thing.
とにかく真実は
At any rate, the fact remains
that that card is the Fool.
あのカードが愚者であること！
正位置を引けば勝てる！
If he draws that one, we can win.
He can turn 40 to one odds into 20 to one.
40分の１が２分の１になるんだ！
（鈴井）うっ
そのカードにすんの？
You gonna pick that card?
じゃ 開いて
Okay, turn it over.
（鈴井）ぐっ…
No. This isn't it.
This is the one card I can't draw!
いや これじゃない
これだけはダメだ！
はあ？
な… 何やってんですか!?
- What the hell are you doing?
- Whoa.
（るな）
おっと〜 それ以上 しゃべると…
One more word out of you, and...
（鈴井）
会長が なんで
このカードに印を付けたのか
I don't know why the president placed
that mark on this card.
僕には分からない
But there's just one thing I'm sure of.
でも １つだけ確かなことがある
Whether this card is the Fool or not,
which position I should draw it in,
このカードは愚者なのか否か
どちら向きで引くべきか
このカードを引くにあたって
負うリスク
the risk I'm taking by drawing this card.
それは全部
会長が用意したものだってこと！
All that... It was all provided by you,
President. Taking on risk is the fun part.
リスクを負うのが楽しいんだ
そのいちばん大事なところを
人に任せていいわけがない！
Nobody would leave that most crucial task
to someone else. It's my choice to make!
（夢子）はっ！
（鈴井）選ぶのは僕だ！
（夢子）ハア
I'm gonna decide what risk I'm gonna take.
自分で負うリスクは自分で決める！
（夢子）ハア ハア
This is my gamble!
（鈴井）これが
これが僕のギャンブルだ！
（夢子）すご〜い！
Amazing!
ええ ええ すばらしい！
Yes! That's splendid! Let's just pick
at random. Let's leave it all to chance.
ぜひとも
適当に選びましょう
運任せに選びましょう！
ただし…
However... I insist you do it
with your own hand!
あくまで自らの手で！
さあ…
Now, then...
let's get our gambling freak on.
賭け狂いましょう
（２人）わっ
Judgment in the upright position!
Plus 20 points, so a total of zero points.
（るな）正位置の審判！
プラス20点で合計ゼロ点！
よって
運命のタロットは引き分け〜！
Therefore, the Tarot Cards of Fate
has ended in a draw.
（鈴井）ハア ハア ハア ハア…
ハア
Neither one of you has to leave
the academy.
どちらも学園を去らなくてもいいよ
よかったね お疲れさん
- Good for you. And good job, President.
- President!
（清華）会長！
（綺羅莉）ん…
会長
President...
よかった
I'm so glad.
あっ
あっ！
しっかりなさい 清華
Get a hold of yourself, Sayaka.
あっ…
（夢子）鈴井さん
（鈴井）あっ
Suzui.
夢子
Yumeko...
（伊月）何やってんすか 先輩！
（鈴井）わっ！
What were you thinking, senpai?
If you'd drawn the Fool, you could've won.
愚者を引けば２分の１で勝てたのに
なんで わざわざ捨てたんですか!?
- Why'd you deliberately throw it away?
- Well, you know, like I said...
いや だから それはさっき…
（芽亜里）
皇(すめらぎ) あんた 何言ってんの？
Sumeragi, what are you talking about?
あんな
分かりやすい印が付いたカードが
A card marked so blatantly...
There's no way that was the Fool.
愚者なわけないでしょ
はあ？ でも会長は
愚者にしか触っていませんでしたよ
But the Fool was the only card
the president touched.
No, she must've been holding
two stuck together.
いやいや
２枚重ねて持ってたんでしょ
愚者の後ろには
別のカードがあったのよ
ホントに愚者だったら
自分で引かないわけないでしょ？
If it was the Fool, there's no way
she wouldn't draw it herself.
（伊月）いいえ
No! You just don't know, Saotome-senpai,
but the president would stoop to that.
早乙女(さおとめ)先輩は知らないでしょうけど
会長はそういうことします！
（芽亜里）
んなわけないでしょ
バカじゃない？
She wouldn't. Are you an idiot?
- Do you want to check?
- Wouldn't have it any other way.
じゃあ 確認してみますか!?
（芽亜里）望むところよ！
（るな）ニャハハハハ！
（芽亜里）ああ！
（伊月）ちょ… 何してんすか！
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
こういうのは
知らないほうが楽しいって！
It's more fun not to know
these kinds of things.
Hey, you! Those are my tarot cards!
（伊月）
ちょっと！
それ 私のタロットですよ〜
Who knew it would end in a draw?
I think I might really become a fatalist.
（綺羅莉）まさか 引き分けとわね
本当に運命論者になってしまいそう
私もです
I think I might, too. There must be
a more thrilling fate in store for us.
きっとこのあとは
もっともっと楽しい運命が
待っているんでしょうね！
フッ 夢子
Yumeko, those are some fine underlings
you have there.
あなた いい従者を持ったわね
At this rate... Oh, yes. I'm sure it will
be even more entertaining after this.
この分なら… ええ きっと
このあとは もっと面白くなる
No.
（夢子）
いいえ
従者なんかじゃありませんよ
They aren't my underlings, you know.
私は とってもいい
お友達を持ちました
What I've found are some amazing friends.
（綺羅莉）フッ
（るな）
あっ もしも〜し
留守電 聞いてくれた？
Hey. Hello?
Did you listen to my voicemail?
Things were insane over here!
Yumeko and the president's gamble...
すごかったよ〜 こっちは
夢子と会長のギャンブル
ニャハ 見逃して残念だったね！
Too bad you missed it, huh?
It was so much fun.
面白かったのに〜
蛇喰夢子は 思ったよりすごいね
Yumeko Jabami is even more amazing
than I thought.
Even the president might
not be able to handle her.
こりゃ 会長も
どうにか なっちゃうかもよ〜
ねえ…
You know...
Ririka Momobami?
桃喰(ももばみ)リリカ
Hyakkao Private Academy.
（鈴井）
私立百花王学園
夢子が来てからというもの
Ever since Yumeko arrived here,
her existence caused
an untold number of people to change.
たくさんの人が
彼女の存在によって変わった
家畜から人間になった者
Those who rose from house pets to humans.
憧れに決着をつけた者
Those who came to terms
with their yearning.
敗北にまみれた者
Those who became mired in defeat.
信仰を得た者
Those who found religion.
（妄(みだり)）ウヘッ 夢子〜
Yumeko.
ハア アハハハ アハハハ…
（鈴井）
そして
And...
新たな獲物に
舌なめずりをする者
those who lick their chops
before new prey.
（綺羅莉）
ただいまをもって
生徒会を解散するわ
As of this moment,
I'm going to dissolve the student council.
But Yumeko herself hasn't changed.
（鈴井）
でも 夢子は変わらない
Even after hundreds of millions, billions
of gambles, she continues to seek it out.
何億 何十億の勝負を経ても
まだ求め続ける
彼女は まともじゃない
She's not normal.
ギャンブル狂
A gambling freak.
賭ケグルイだ
A compulsive gambler.
THE WOMAN
WHO'S A COMPULSIVE GAMBLER
〜